Bien.
This is the proposal.
The Aspen estate becomes a hotel.
I already have
your grandfather's signature.
Now we just need yours.
This house.
It's all that's left of my parents.
It's their memory.
But who am I even telling this to?
You don't understand
what family means.
A real family.
Maybe.
But I do understand business.
And I know that this house
drains a lot of money every month.
It can make it instead.
No!
You’ve already sold off
all the family’s antiques!
Isn't that enough for you?
Oh, have you forgotten?
I forget nothing.
And this house,
it's just a building
with floor, walls and roof.
It will never bring back your parents
and your brother.
Don't you dare say so.
You grew up among savages.
So nothing is sacred to you.
Veronica, stop.
Okay.
Come on. Shoot me.